woodhouseclothing.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy

**FREE Next Day UK Delivery** \- on all orders over £150

 **FREE UK Returns** \- from 2,500 drop off locations

 **7 Days a Week** \- now delivering on Sundays

## PRIVACY STATEMENT

We take the security and privacy of our customers seriously and this policy sets out how we handle information about you and your rights in respect of that information.

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE HOLD AND HOW DO WE OBTAIN IT?

Generally we receive information directly from you when you place an order with us to buy our goods. Such information includes your name, address, telephone number and credit card details. You may also provide your email address if you sign up to be notified from time to time about our future goods and services.

For our customers' protection, we always check a certain percentage of our orders at random to confirm the details of the order match those of the cardholder on file. For this reason, we may ask you for some additional information. This would be a copy of the front and back of the card used to make the purchase, or a copy of a photo ID such as a valid drivers license or passport. We will also require some proof of address along with the copy of the photo ID.

## FOR WHAT PURPOSES DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?

We use your information for a number of purposes including:

  * to perform our contractual obligations to you and to ensure that goods are supplied to you as efficiently as possible
  * for other non-contractual reasons.

## SUPPLYING GOODS TO YOU

  * We may use your information:
  * To identify and maintain records of your purchases with us
  * To ensure that the goods and services we offer to you are appropriate for your needs
  * To respond to any query you may raise with us about our goods
  * To update our systems for providing you with an enhanced service
  * Other purposes

We will also use information about you for purposes upon which the provision of our goods and services are not necessarily dependent.

## WE MAY:

  * Disclose information about you to third party agencies for credit checking purposes (which information may be shared with other organisations for the same purpose)
  * Use information about you to inform you (by post email or telephone) about other services we offer or which are offered by other companies within our group or any of the other companies with which we work
  * Use information about your account with us for our internal customer service monitoring and training purposes

## TRANSFERS OVERSEAS

The internet is a global network, so it is possible for your data to travel internationally, which may include places outside the European Union. If you visit or shop at woodhouseclothing.com, you're agreeing and authorising us to process data in this way.

## SALE OF OUR BUSINESS

You acknowledge that data you provide to us may be transferred to any person, firm or company to whom we sell the whole or a substantial part of our business or to whom we transfer any of our rights or obligations under a contract with you.

## TAKING CARE OF YOUR DATA

We will endeavor to keep any information, which we hold, about you up to date and accurate. To help us to do this, please keep us informed if any of your details change.

We will endeavor to protect your data against unauthorised use.

## Right to access your personal information

The Data Protection Act 1998 gives you the right to access information held about you. You can obtain access to your personal information held by us by putting your request in writing and sending a cheque for £10 (to cover administration costs for collating this information), made payable to Clothingsites.co.uk Ltd, The Studios, Dallimore Road, Roundthorn Industrial Estate, MANCHESTER, M23 9NX. If you have any questions about Clothingsites.co.uk Ltd's Data Protection Policy please write to our Data Protection Officer or e-mail us at dataprivacy@clothingsites.co.uk

## MARKETING OPT-OUT

By submitting your email address to one of the forms which can be found throughout our website, you are agreeing to receive a newsletter and/or email marketing campaigns from us, which you can easily opt out from at any time. By registering for a Woodhouse account, you will also be subscribed to our mailing list.

**WHAT TYPE OF EMAIL WILL I RECEIVE?**  
Around three times a week, you will receive an email containing exclusive offers, useful tips and our personal pick of the latest fashions.

**WHO WILL I RECEIVE EMAIL FROM?**  
You will only ever receive email from Woodhouse. We never share your information with third parties so you can rest assured that you won't be receiving any spam.

At any time, you can tell us that you do not want us to use your details for the purposes of marketing. You can opt-out from all future communications from Woodhouse by using the unsubscribe link from any of our email communications, or emailing us at customerservices@woodhouseclothing.com or by writing to us at:

Woodhouse Marketing Department, The Studios, Dallimore Road, Roundthorn Industrial Estate, MANCHESTER, M23 9NX.

If you have any further questions, don't hesitate to contact our Customer Service team on +44 (0) 161 413 3640.

## COOKIES

As part of ensuring the proper operation of our site and to maximise your enjoyment of it, we currently use cookies on this website. On 26th May 2012 the rules about the use of cookies on websites changed. A cookie is a small file, typically of letters and numbers, downloaded to your device when you visit our website and allows us and/or our business partners to recognise you as a user when you return using the same computer and web browser. You can find an overview of the various types of cookies used by us and/or our business partners, in the table below.

Cookie type | Purpose  
---|---  
Essential | We use cookies to keep track of what you have in your basket, and to remember you when you return to our site. Without cookies, the site would forget which items you placed in your basket and you wouldn't be able to buy anything.  
Functional | When you register with us, we generate cookies that signal whether you are signed in or not. Our servers use these cookies to work out which account you are signed in with, and serve you any content/data specific to your account. These cookies get deleted when you either close your browser or shut down your computer.  
Analytics | These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. [**More information on Google Analytics**](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html)  
Third Party | 

We work with third party companies for marketing and advertising purposes. These cookies allow us to make more informed decisions about what our customers want from us. Any information that they collect is anonymous. Because of how cookies work, we cannot access these cookies, nor can the third parties access the data in cookies used by us.

**Third parties we work with and why**

**Google AdWords**  
AdWords uses cookies to anonymously identify traffic and conversions from paid search advertisements, recording data like the amount of items purchased, the value of those items and the time of day the purchase was made. This cookie is placed on a user’s browser via a redirect to the destination landing page. We can then use this information to improve our display ads.

**Webgains**  
Webgains use cookies to anonymously record that a user has clicked on an Webgains link that referred the user to our site. This information is collected in order to enable us to pay a commission to Webgains and its affiliates for any sales they may drive on our site. Webgains cookies remain active for a period of 30 days.

**AddThis**  
AddThis use cookies to record when you have interacted with their widget. When you share a product using the social media sharing button on our site, the social network that has created the button will record that you have done this.

**Struq**  
Struq places anonymous cookies which collect details of pages and products you viewed. This information is then used to better direct advertisements shown to you on 3rd party websites to make sure that those adverts include products that are of interest to you.

**VisualDNA**  
We use a tag of a third-party service provider, VisualDNA, to anonymously collect information about users' browsing activity on our website (this does not include names, addresses or any other personal information). This information is linked to a cookie that VisualDNA sets in your browser. This information allows us and VisualDNA to build a profile so that your online experience can be made more relevant to your specific interests. You have the right to opt out from VisualDNA's service by clicking [here](http://my.visualdna.com/) and choosing the 'Cookie Settings' option.

VisualDNA does not store or share personally identifiable information with any third party, other than in anonymised, aggregated form.

To learn more, visit VisualDNA's privacy policy at [http://www.visualdna.com/privacy-policy](http://www.visualdna.com/privacy-policy/) and VisualDNA's cookie policy at [http://www.visualdna.com/cookie-policy](http://www.visualdna.com/cookie-policy/).  
  
If you want to manage your cookies then you can do this via your browser or alternatively please visit [**www.aboutcookies.org**](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for up to date information about cookie management. All modern browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. These settings will typically be found in the 'options' or 'preferences' menu of your browser. In order to understand these settings, see the 'Help' option in your browser for more details.

Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able fully use our website. We have taken all reasonable steps to notify you of our use of cookies, your use of this site without disabling cookies is considered as your express consent for us to use cookies for the purposes set out above.
